

MATTHEW MADDOCK

mattmaddock00@hotmail.com | 443 537 0625 | 9209 Maple Rock Dr , Ellicott City , MD 21042

Summary

With 4 years of film production experience and education behind him, Matthew Maddock is currently a visual effects artist and videographer, living in Ellicott City, USA. Matthew is a certified Adobe Premiere professional winning awards for his short films, including "Echoes" in the Howard County Film Festival 2018 where the film won judges choice for best cinematography and story. His career led him to Howard Community College where he is seeking an associate degree in Audio, Video Media Production.

Skills

- Quick learner
- Excellent communication
- Works well with kids
- Excel in video editing and visual effects
- Experience in cinematography
- Proficiency in DSLR/Mirrorless camera use

Experience

Educator

06/2017 - 09/2020

ClubSci Kidz | Elkridge MD

Teaching elementary school children science through after school programs and summer camps.

Teaching middle school children science through after school programs and summer camps.

Coach/Volunteer 01/2016 - Current

Special Olympics Maryland | Baltimore MD

Coaching Athletes in different sports including, Snowshoe, Basketball, and Volleyball.

Also worked as a volunteer at different events.

Awarded the Schnorf Family Scholarship for Outstanding Student Volunteer.

Graphic Design Intern

07/2019 - 09/2018

Medifast/Optavia | Baltimore MD

Editing videos and creating motion graphics to be used in events.

Made videos for promotion and recognition

Education and

High School Diploma

2018

Mount Hebron High School | Ellicott City, MD

Currently Enrolled

Expected 2021

Howard Community College | Baltimore, MD

Websites,

Training

MattSMaddock.github.io

Portfolios, Profiles

- Mattlore_Visuals (Instagram)
- Mattlore (Youtube)

Certifications

Video Communication using Adobe Premiere Pro CS6, Certiport